const contest_3_3 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Iron (II) sulphide, obtained by passing $\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{~S}$ through a solution of iron (II) salt is black in colour.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Inorganic Chemistry", "Iron Compounds"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "When dilute ammonia is added dropwise to iron (III) solution, a reddish-brown precipitate is formed, which dissolves in excess ammonia.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Inorganic Chemistry", "Precipitation Reactions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Bubbling $\\mathrm{H}_{2} \\mathrm{~S}$ gas through a solution of zinc ions gives a white precipitate.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Inorganic Chemistry", "Precipitation Reactions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "When ammonia is heated strongly with ethanoyl chloride, ethylamine is formed.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "F. Ethanamide is formed.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Organic Chemistry", "Amides"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Secondary alkanols produce alkanones when oxidized with acidified $\\mathrm{K}_{2} \\mathrm{Cr}_{2} \\mathrm{O}_{7}$ solution.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "T.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Organic Chemistry", "Oxidation Reactions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The bites of ants itch because ants inject ethanoic acid into the bite.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "F. Methanoic acid.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Organic Chemistry", "Acids"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The terrestrial magnetic field is horizontal everywhere on the surface of the earth.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Terrestrial Magnetism", "Physics Concepts"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The terrestrial magnetic field varies with time.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Terrestrial Magnetism", "Physics Concepts"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The terrestrial magnetic field is mainly a magnetic dipole field.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Terrestrial Magnetism", "Physics Concepts"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "An object is projected from level ground at an angle to the horizontal. Air resistance and other non-idealities are negligible.",
        "Question": "The horizontal range of the object increases then decreases as the angle of projection is increased from zero to $90^{\\circ}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Projectile Motion", "Kinematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "An object is projected from level ground at an angle to the horizontal. Air resistance and other non-idealities are negligible.",
        "Question": "The horizontal range of the object is greatest when the angle of projection is $45^{\\circ}$.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Projectile Motion", "Kinematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "An object is projected from level ground at an angle to the horizontal. Air resistance and other non-idealities are negligible.",
        "Question": "For a fixed angle of projection, the horizontal range varies linearly with speed of projection.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "False",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Projectile Motion", "Kinematics"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Plants with evergreen leaves whose epidermis is heavily cutinized or with waxy cell walls show greater resistance of desiccation under conditions of extreme soil dryness.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Plant Adaptations", "Cutinization"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "In angiosperms, reproductive organs are more sensitive to drought than vegetative organs",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Plant Adaptations", "Drought Sensitivity"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "One of the most important adaptations of true xerophytes is the production of extensive root system in proportion to shoot system.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Plant Adaptations", "Root Systems"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The most abundant lipid which is present in the plasma membrane is a phospholipid which contains a polar head group attached to two hydrophobic fatty acid tails.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Phospholipids", "Cell Membranes"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The peripheral proteins in the plasma membrane function as to provide fluidity as well as mechanical support to the structure of the cell.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Peripheral Proteins", "Cell Membranes"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The plasma membrane generates and distributes signals in and outside of the cell for the proper functioning of the cell and all the organelles.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "True",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Signal Transduction", "Cell Membranes"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$4 a^{2}+6 a b+9 b^{2}=(2 a+3 b)^{2}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Binomial Expansion"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$(5 a-2 b)^{2}=25 a^{2}-20 a b+4 b^{2}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "TRUE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Binomial Expansion"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "$9 a^{2}+24 a b+16 b^{2}=(3 a+4 b)^{2}$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "TRUE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Algebra", "Binomial Expansion"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A triangle fits its outline in three positions.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Symmetry", "Geometric Shapes"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A parallelogram fits its outline in two positions.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "TRUE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Symmetry", "Geometric Shapes"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A square fits its outline in 4 positions.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "FALSE",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Symmetry", "Geometric Shapes"]
    }
]

export default contest_3_3